Everybody knows Jay Kelly, but Jay Kelly doesn't know himself.
Jay Kelly is a drama, comedy film directed by Noah Baumbach.
Famous movie actor Jay Kelly embarks on a journey of self-discovery, confronting
both his past and present, accompanied by his devoted manager, Ron.
Jay Kelly, played by George Clooney.
Ron Sukenick, played by Adam Sandler.
Liz, played by Laura Dern.
Timothy, played by Billy Crudup.
Jessica Kelly, played by Riley Keough.
Daisy Kelly, played by Grace Edwards.
Jay Kelly is a 2025 comedy-drama film directed by Noah
Baumbach and written by Baumbach and Emily Mortimer.
The film stars an ensemble cast that includes George Clooney,
Adam Sandler, Laura Dern, and Billy Crudup.
It follows a famous actor (Clooney) as he travels through Europe with his team and manager
(Sandler), and reflects on his life choices, relationships, and legacy.
The film had its world premiere in the main competition of the 82nd
Venice International Film Festival on August 28, 2025.
It was then released in select theaters on November 14, 2025,
followed by a global release on Netflix on December 5.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with
praise for Clooney and Sandler's performances.
Both Clooney and Sandler received acting nominations at the 83rd
Golden Globe Awards for their performances in the film.
The film explores themes of manager, europe, nostalgic, dramedy, actor.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.